[Gold List Title]
Come on…
Sister Jina
Oh, it’s Yeli
You know you are the hope of Caihua Girls High School, right?
I wish you the best in the college entrance examination. Come on!
We'll cheer you up
Thank you...thank you
Hello
Jay…
I've always been afraid of you
Sister Jina, come on
Come on
Especially your dark eyes
[Mathematics]
It's like you know everything
Laughing coldly at my expression
It's driving me crazy
All this is because of you Liu Jieyi
no one will know
To be a sister who is less useful than a younger sister
How sad is it
I just want to beat you
Get dad's love again
When my father found out about my relationship with the teacher...
He praised me
Something I've never felt before...
That warm compliment
I heard you had a daughter who disappeared thirteen years ago.
Stop looking for it
why
Why did you say that suddenly?
Didn't we agree to find it at least this year?
What about you?
why do you want to find her
Because I found her...
You might be willing to accept our child
Whether Seulgi is found or not...
Neither of us can have children.
Give up
[Searching for missing children]
Yu Seqi…
I refuse
Of course I wouldn't ask for your help in vain.
i am willing to pay the price
There's no need
I'll pretend I didn't hear it
I can help you find your daughter
The two of us who are fathers
Let’s work hard together
Sister Jie Na knows that the teacher has a missing daughter
Are you just taking advantage of this?
I swear I never told anyone that
[Daejundong Valet Delivery Service]
Hello…
Hello
teacher
I heard that Teacher Kim Sun Young
Because of breach of confidentiality agreement
Expelled from the University Entrance Examination Proposal Committee
Wow my great and almighty father…
Found your daughter
[Yu Seqi]
[Probability of parent-child relationship 99.98%]
It’s been thirteen years and it’s not easy to find my daughter.
You probably don't want her to receive this video, right?
Teacher, please hand over your phone
[The day before the big exam]
The plan is simple
Eat the devil-level problem
Then leave the question dormitory
["Good-natured Competition"]
Heavenly Father, Lord of the Living and the Dead
We are gathered here today
Funeral service held for Sister Liu Jiena who was called by the Lord
We are born from dust and we will return to dust
Believe that everything is under the control of Heavenly Father...
All the family members are here
You're going to be ready for burial soon, right?
Although Sister Liu Jiena’s body will leave us
But we believe that on the day of glory of the Lord
She will be resurrected in a glorious body
meet us again
We will say goodbye today
Although it is a short farewell...
Liu Jieyi
You feel something is wrong too, right?
what
This corpse is not Sister Jina’s
Look, she has burn scars on her feet
Does your sister have such wounds on her feet?
your dad
Have a very special interest
He will collect unknown corpses
Use them to practice surgery
This person is the sister I met in the kindergarten
Cui Xiuzhen
She died because no one claimed her
I owe the funeral home a large sum of money for storage fees.
I've heard of these unknown corpses
In the end, they will all be sent to your home hospital.
What’s even more coincidental is Cui Xiuzhen…
Live next door to your sister
Could these be coincidences?
So that's it
As a doctor and a family member
From declaration of death to confirmation of identity
It's too easy to cover the sky with one hand
And a suicide note was found
So seamless
what are you doing
Do you want Cui Xiuzhen to become your sister?
Yeah
Then Sister Jina will really disappear from this world
If dad's plan is to let her "die"
Of course let him continue to commit crimes
It's better for us, isn't it?
If we expose him now, we'll screw up the funeral.
He will definitely think of another way
He is a person who will not give up easily
So the most important thing now is...
We can't let him know that we already know
Let's go
If you want to go, go by yourself
I can't leave like this
I…
I read your sister's diary
It says…
How did my dad die?
I must find evidence
Don't be stupid
You will be discovered before you find the evidence.
follow me
I'll help you delay
You have to move quickly
Oh
Miss
My mother said it was not a happy event after all
It's best not to reveal the identities of the guests
So let me ask you to turn off the monitor
Until my sister’s funeral ceremony is over
Then I'll go check with the dean...
Because it's my mother's request
It's not the dean's request
That's why she sent me
My sister is having a funeral. Where did you go?
What about mom?
My sister has become like this, where are you?
Smile, isn’t this what you’re best at?
Ah, no
Should I cry today?
Aren't you a doctor?
Why can't he even save his own daughter?
Do patients dare to come to you for treatment like this?
Forget it, weak kids go early
It’s a relief for parents
Jay, you’ve grown so big
I heard you got good grades
It's really nerve-wracking to have this kind of thing happen to me in my senior year of high school.
Every minute and second during this period is precious
Only students who are cramming need to worry
Even if I don’t study for three days
It won't be affected, right uncle?
Oh my God, this kid is with you
It's like it was carved out of the same mold
Thanks for the compliment
Jay
Dad knows everything
He knows who the "good boys" are
Who is the "bad boy"
How
Can't you figure it out?
Do you want my help?
Are you here specifically to show off?
Now is not the time to sit around in a daze, right?
I don't need your help, get out
Get out of here
Go away…
I can't cry, absolutely not
Because dads don't give gifts to crying children
This sounds like the lyrics to a Christmas song
but what is the gift
Sister Jina, do you want any gifts?
I don't know either
But Liu Jiena is very similar to her father
Very obsessed with birthdays and Christmas
There are various anniversaries
The day before last year’s university entrance exam…
It's November 15th
♫On the abandoned road♫
♫I can’t bear it and want to cry♫
♫Can’t understand why I fell in love silently♫
No Seulgi
aunt
Liu Jiena
A woman’s sixth sense is always very accurate
Although I don’t want to take it to heart
[Teacher, this keychain is like my guardian angel]
but no way
That kid…
Always around us
[I will arrive later
I will bring your husband’s mobile phone over]
After your father passed away...
those weird things that happened
At first…
I thought it was the kid who did it
[Liu Jiena is dead]
But maybe Zena wants to tell us something.
Please give way
Who doesn't know that they accused you of stealing drugs at that time?
Just to force me to compromise and sign a settlement document
You won't...sign it?
No
I insist not to sign
They actually asked me
Is it because I am your stepmother?
Do you think so too?
No
you did the right thing
where are you going
Please help me get it
And…
Please help stop the lawyer and don't let her follow you.
Seulgi
Me?
scared me
what are you doing
You also know the truth of the matter, right?
what
Don't try to lie to me
I know the rent owed by Sister Xiuzhen and the credit account
You paid it back for her
so
Are you here to see her off on her last journey today?
If there is no one to handle it, forget about the funeral...
She can only lie in the icehouse all the time
rotting alone
At least now she got on the hearse in style.
You should think so too
do you really think so
If there is any humanity left
You should be more concerned about sister Xiuzhen's death
It's okay to feel guilty
Yes, if you have a conscience
We would not have been induced to take drugs in the first place
Hello
Get off the bus
You’re not here just for Xiuzhen, right?
These X-rays cannot be used as evidence
why
why not
Even if you are right
This is really a college entrance exam question
There is no way to prove that he was disemboweled.
Died while taking things out
Concealing the patient’s true condition
It is indeed medical negligence.
But it must be directly proven that these actions resulted in death
The difficulty is too high
Not to mention proving that they had the intent to kill.
Such an inference is too radical
There are hundreds of these vinyl records
On his side…
Kill...
while listening to music
Maybe I heard it when I was rescuing people.
have you heard this song
Yeah
It's a song by Lucid Fall
Sister Jenna likes it very much...
Oh my god
That means the things written in the diary are true.
She was actually taken into the operating room
There are no monitors in the operating room
There must be testimony from the parties involved
Or at least be able to prove it
The diary was written by Jina
But the only witness is gone
what is this
I received it after my husband died.
Sender…
Know the relationship between Jie Na and him
Could this person be another witness?
Maybe it was someone who was in the operating room at the time.
Or people who are in the dormitory where the entrance exam questions are asked
Maybe someone from school
If Anonymous really knows key information
It should be written in the letter
Choosing to be anonymous means there is a reason
He doesn't want to reveal his identity
Generally, even if the whistleblower is found in such a case,
It is also difficult to persuade the other party to testify in court
When is our next court date?
What's wrong
I understand you don't want to give up hope
But as I said just now, based on this evidence alone
There is no way to prove that he was killed
Unless the deceased can come back and testify personally
Stop playing detective games
Concentrate on preparing for college entrance exams
if i were a lawyer
A key witness like me
There should be many questions to ask
But mom doesn’t seem to be like this
Also
You're already into this kind of thing
I'm not interested in a medical lawsuit that makes no money, right?
But he pretends to be considerate of his client
Pretending to be a good lawyer...
-Cui Jing…
-You do the same to me
Pretending to be a good mother
Pretending to be a decent parent
But in fact they are all fake
You don't want to know how I know
Is there a relationship between Teacher Yu Daohe and Liu Jiena?
Yeah
I don't want to know at all
you may not know
My hobby is masturbation
That day I ran to school in the middle of the night to masturbate
Because the night before the exam
Masturbating in the classroom helps me feel less anxious
Just like that, I happened to bump into him
Teacher Yu Daohe and Liu Jiena together
I wanted to tell someone about this
But if you say it out loud, people will definitely ask
Why were you there at that time?
I can't answer it at all
So I can only stay silent
I really want Jay to die
Without her, I would have won first place
Because of her, no one will ever notice me
I've really had enough
When I met Sister Jina on the day of school anniversary
I told her...
I know everything
if she doesn't tell the truth
I will tell everything
But she died
I'm scared every day now
I think it's my fault
But you, the mother, can only ask me to study.
Liu Jiena's death
It has nothing to do with you
The same goes for the death of teacher Yu Daohe
You will never testify in court
So you are not allowed to say these words to anyone.
Did you hear that? Cui Jing
This is the advice your lawyer mother gave you.
[Business Club]
Sister, you are here
Can't you get zopiclone?
Sleeping pills?
I'll go find out
Don't sell to anyone else. Give me all the goods.
I'll buy it from you at a high price
Good
Help me buy a pack of cigarettes. No need for change.
thank you
welcome
What are you doing? Is something wrong?
You and Seulgi really have the same chemistry.
Don't compare me to her
I'm much prettier than her
No matter how much I think about it, I don’t think this business is worthwhile.
Kang Suting in the nightclub last time
You took it secretly
Did you see Liu Jiena at Jiangnan Station?
Didn't tell me either
Why cooperate if we are so suspicious of each other?
I might as well do it alone.
Compared to a high school girl like you
I am more persuasive when discussing business
So can you get zopiclone?
If we could control J Medical Center
What are the sleeping pills?
Just wait
But…
A model student from a wealthy family like Jai Yi
Why sell medicine?
Hey, don't try to understand her
Her brain structure is different from ours
Don't keep saying "we" and confuse me with you.
Very unpleasant
Aunt, how much are these?
Add another plate of pork blood sausage
That's a total of 5,000 won
thank you
Anyway, you'd better be careful
That person is scarier than you think
Seulgi’s father…
He was the one who killed him, right?
Please keep your promise
I will contact you again